BRYAN JUSTIN PALAD

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / FRONT END ENGINEER





+63-945-560-2846



✓ paladbryanj@gmail.com



്ന് Bryan-Justin-Palad



bryanpalad.vercel.app (portfolio)



Brgy.Banlic, Cabuyao City, Laguna

PROFILE

Enthusiastic software developer with 3 years of experience in software and web development, inclusive of 1+ year of hands-on work experience specifically in web development. Currently looking for a challenging role where I can keep learning, work on exciting projects, and be part of a vibrant team. Excited to bring my skills to a company that values creativity, teamwork, and growth.

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

- Dedicated and Hardworking individual.
- · Highly adaptable, Flexible, Well disciplined and keen on details.
- Fast learner and have a strong will to learn new technologies.
- · Problem Solver, Resilient

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Proficient in:

JavaScript ES6, VueJS, ReactJS, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Responsive Web Design

Familiar using:

NextJS, Typescript, React Redux, Vuex, RESTful API Integration, Java (Spring Boot), MyBatis, PHP, Jest

Frameworks used: Bootstrap, Material UI, Ant Design, Tailwind CSS, UniApp, Aceternity UI

Tools used: MySQL, PostgreSQL, Github, VS Code, NPM, Gitlab, Postman, Figma, Confluence, ClickUP

Other skills: Agile Scrum Methodology, MS Office and PC TroubleShooting.

EDUCATION

COLLEGE LEVEL

STI College Calamba **BS** Information Technology June 2015 - June 2019

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

eMandarin Ventures Inc. (Bonifacio Global City, Taguig) December 12, 2022 - August 19, 2024 (1yr & 8 months)

Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6, VueJS, Vuex, UniApp, Tailwind CSS

Back-End: Java Spring Boot, Spring MVC, MyBatis, Redis, MySQL, Thymeleaf

Tools used: Git, Gitlab, Npm, HBuilder, VSCode, Intellij Idea, DataGrip,

Postman, Termius, Figma

- Led the development of the e-Wallet (PayLoro), specializing in front-end development with VueJS, Vuex, Axios, UniApp and **RESTful API integration**
- Collaborated with graphic/web designer to conceptualize the e-Wallet design using Figma, translating wireframes into a userfriendly interfaces.
- Maintained and innovated the Payment Gateway system (SaaS) using Java Spring Boot, Spring MVC, MyBatis, Redis, Thymeleaf, and MySQL, ensuring efficient and effective tracking of business transactions.
- Developed RESTful APIs with Java Spring Boot, utilizing MyBatis for data handling and MySQL for queries. Integrated these APIs with the e-Wallet using Axios and tested endpoints with Postman.
- · Payment API Integration from companies like Coins.ph, Bayad Center, NetBank, and StarPay. This involved reviewing API documentation, ensuring compatibility, and integrating with our payment gateway and e-Wallet (PayLoro) using JWT and OAuth 2.0 for secure transactions.
- Developed front-end websites, including QRPH, Checkout Counter, and PayBills pages, integrating them with our payment gateway and e-Wallet using VueJS, Vuex, Axios, and TailwindCSS.

TRAININGS & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

August 2024 - Current

NCLEXPower (Senior Front-End Developer)

 Developing a large-scale project focusing on advanced web development using Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, JEST and Agile scrum methodology best practices. Using Confluence for documentation and ClickUp for project management.

July 2022 - Nov 2022

Modern Resolve Organization (Front-End Developer)

• Internal Ecommerce Project focusing on advanced web development using React JS, PostgreSQL, Python Django, Tailwind CSS and Agile scrum methodology for team collaboration.

June 2022 May 2022 March - April 2022

Online Course (Great Learning)

Online Course (TestDome)

Online Course (Simplilearn)

• <u>Java</u> and <u>PHP</u> Course Certificate • <u>Web Developer</u> Certificate

• React JS and Javascript Course Certificate

STI College Calamba S.Y 2018

Lead Programmer (PHP, Bootstrap, MySQL)

Patient Information and Online Appointment System for Fernandez Dental Clinic (with automatic sms and email reminder)

STI College Calamba S.Y 2017

• Lead Programmer (C#, MySQL, Crystal Reports)

Point of Sales and Inventory System for Southern Sky Hardware and Construction Supply